<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ACM_App_GeorgeChan</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Information</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us will go here in the future</string>
    <string name="homepage">Welcome to the ACM App!</string>
    <string name="resources">The Resources will go here in the future</string>
    <string name="announcements">The Announcmenets will go here</string>
    <string name="what_desc">1. To be organized and operated exclusively for educational and scientific purposes to promote:\n
                      - An increased knowledge of and greater interest in the science, design, development, construction, languages, management and applications of modern computing.\n
                      - Greater interest in computing and its applications.\n
                      - A means of communication between persons having an interest in computing.\n
                      - A collective effort among the computing machinery students in marketing their skills to the vast and high-paying computing job industry.\n
                      2. To serve students at Cal State L.A. and other interested persons in the Los Angeles community.</string>
    <string name="who_desc">The Association for Computing Machinery is an international scientific and educational organization dedicated to advancing the art, science,
        engineering, and application of information technology. The ACM Student Chapter at Cal State LA is among the 430 operating student chapters dedicated to the
        ideals of the national ACM. Our goals are achieved by weekly general meetings, tutoring, member-led workshops, presentations from industry representatives and special events.</string>
    <string name="contact_desc">If you have any questions or concerns about office hours, workshop times, tutoring hours or just want to give us some general feed back, feel free to send us an
        email! You can also reach out to us on our official facebook page and Instagram!</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
